export const quizData = [{
    topic: 'Web Protocols and HTML',
    id: 0,
    question: `Status line is present in which message format?`,
    options: [`Request Message`, `Response Message`, `Both Request and Response Message`, `None of the above`],
    answer: `Response Message`
},{
    topic: 'Web Protocols and HTML',
    id: 1,
    question: `www works on which model?`,
    options: [`Local server`, `Client server`, `3-tier`, `None of the above`],
    answer: `Client Server`
},{
    topic: 'Web Protocols and HTML',
    id: 2,
    question: `World Wide Web is`,
    options: [`Another name of internet`, `Worldwide connection of computers`, `A collection of linked information`, `A collection of worldwide information`],
    answer: `A collection of linked information`
},{
    topic: 'Web Protocols and HTML',
    id: 3,
    question: `Number of digits in the Response status code is`,
    options: [`2`,`3`,`4`,`5`],
    answer: `2`
},{
    topic: 'Web Protocols and HTML',
    id: 4,
    question: `<DT> tag is designed to fit a single line of our web page but <DD> tag will accept a`,
    options: [`2`,`3`,`4`,`5`],
    answer: `2`
},
{
    topic: 'Indian Festivals',
    id: 5,
    question: `The birth of which lord is celebrated every year all across India on Janmashtami festival?`,
    options: [`Vishnu`, `Shiva`, `Ganesha`, `Krishna`],
    answer: `Krishna`
},{
    topic: 'Indian Festivals',
    id: 6,
    question: `On which date Christmas is celebrated every year?`,
    options: [`25th September`, `25th October`, `25th December`, `25th November`],
    answer: `25th December`
},{
    topic: 'Indian Festivals',
    id: 7,
    question: `Onam, the harvest festival, is celebrated in which state of India?`,
    options: [`Andhra Pradesh`,`Kerala`,`Maharashtra`, `Karnataka`],
    answer: `Kerala`
},{
    topic: 'Indian Festivals',
    id: 8,
    question: `Lohri, the harvest festival, is celebrated in which Indian state?`,
    options: [`Assam`, `Meghalaya`, `West Bengal`, `Punjab`],
    answer: `Punjab`
},{
    topic: 'Indian Festivals',
    id: 9,
    question: `5.People of which religion celebrate Good Friday?`,
    options: [`Hindus`,`Sikhs`,`Jains`, `Christians`],
    answer: `Christians`
},{
    topic: 'Basics of Computer Science',
    id: 10,
    question: `1 Terabyte (Tb) =`,
    options: [`1024 GB`, `1000 GB`, `1200 GB`, `1275 GB`],
    answer: `1024 GB`
},{
    topic: 'Basics of Computer Science',
    id: 11,
    question: `If the operating system of a computer stops working while working on this, usually what does a user do?`,
    options: [`Leave`, `Restart`, `Format`, `Throw`],
    answer: `Restart`
},{
    topic: 'Basics of Computer Science',
    id: 12,
    question: `The first general purpose programmable electronic computer was`,
    options: [`ENIAC`,`Mac`,`IBM`, `UNEC`],
    answer: `ENIAC`
},{
    topic: 'Basics of Computer Science',
    id: 13,
    question: `Who among the following had first invented microchip?`,
    options: [`Jack Kilby`,`Jack Dorsey`,`Ronald Rider`,`Greg Chesson`],
    answer: `Jack Kilby`
},{
    topic: 'Basics of Computer Science',
    id: 14,
    question: `7. Which among the following is the shortcut key to open the shortcut menu for the active window?`,
    options: [`Alt + F4`,`Ctrl + F6`,`Alt + Spacebar`, `Ctrl + Spacebar`],
    answer: `Alt + Spacebar`
}]